<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Manya Bansal</title>
    <link>https://manya-bansal.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Manya Bansal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://manya-bansal.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mosaic: An Interoperable Compiler for Tensor Algebra</title>
      <link>https://manya-bansal.github.io/posts/mosaic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manya-bansal.github.io/posts/mosaic/</guid>
      <description>Abstract. We introduce Mosaic, a sparse tensor algebra compiler that can bind tensor (sub-)expressions to external functions of other tensor algebra libraries or compilers. Users can extend Mosaic by adding new functions and can bind a sub-computation to a function using a scheduling API. Mosaic substitutes the bound (sub-)expressions with the specified function call and automatically fills in the rest of the unbound code using a default code generator. Mosaic also has a search system that can automatically map an expression to a set of registered external functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use common debugging hardware and traps to build tiny, effective kernel-level dynamic checkers</title>
      <link>https://manya-bansal.github.io/posts/kernel-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manya-bansal.github.io/posts/kernel-tools/</guid>
      <description>Abstract. This paper shows how to use common debugging hardware support for single-step execution to make writing powerful dynamic tools easy &amp;mdash; often a few hundred lines of code. Unlike most current tools, these work well on kernel code. This novel ease makes it correspondingly easy to quickly build novel tools. We present a number of unique tools based on this approach to precisely and immediately find kernel bugs extremely difficult to track down without them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
